(Sheldon:)I know how to
get the bucket!
(Sheldon:)I can turn the axe around
(Sheldon:)and use the handle to reach it.
(Sheldon:)Let's see.
(Sheldon:)Go north.
"You are in a forest."
Oh dear, I believe I'm lost.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'll just have to get
a fresh start tomorrow.
No, no, no! You just
took a wrong turn.
(Leonard:)You just need to map it out.
(Leonard:)Come on, I'll help you.
So you stopped at the stream,
(Leonard:)and you turned
north three times?
(Howard:)Yes.
(Leonard:)You're right.
You're lost. Good luck.
(Priya:)Oh!
(Priya:)Leonard. Wake up.
Huh? Wh-- Sorry.
(Priya:)For what?
(Leonard:)I don't know. When I'm in bed
with a girl, it's just--
it's my go-to response.
It's 6:00. I have
to get back to Raj's
(Priya:)before he wakes up
and realizes I'm gone.
(Leonard:)Oh. Right. Sure.
(Leonard:)I wish you could stay
in L.A. a while longer.